I was talking to my therapist, that's one of the ways that I deal with my mental health.
I went through a very traumatic experience recently, and I was telling my therapist
that I was kind of concerned that I wasn't, like, in pieces on the floor, you know?
It wasn't that I didn't feel it. It wasn't that I haven't been affected by it.
I'm wondering, am I being avoidant? Am I being disconnected?
Like, am I not dealing with this?
And she was like, you know, Amanda, when you are not able to function because of something,
that means you're not dealing with it. It's dealing with you.
She was like, you're not someone who runs from things.
You're not someone who hides from things.
You are absolutely consciously aware of what's taking place.
You're just at a point in your life where you have learned how to manage things
in a fashion that doesn't create dysfunctionality.
You're talking to me because you're managing the thing.
And I was like, growth.